谢谢你们赶过来
我们希望你们能帮 我们想一些婚礼上用的点子
怎么了? 你还好吗? 那只是因为…
莫妮卡说了“婚礼”
我们希望你们之中有人能上台念些感性的文章
好吧，我想我应变也能胜任
也能胜任?
短篇
好吧，那罗斯来读
好的，我想我也能胜任
也能?
我自己想了一个点子，来庆祝你们的婚礼
你能告诉我们是什么点子吗? 抱歉
我想把它当成高度机密
不管你是指哪个，我希望会有眨眼睛
嘿 嘿
我跟《我日》子的编剧谈过…
什么是《我日》? 《我们的日子》
你们一定不相信 我演的角色就要醒过来了
那真的是太棒了哇，乔伊
不只是那个，我会有个新脑子!
你的工作跟私生活都有了很棒的进展
你要换个新脑子?
他们要踢走剧中一个角色…
将她的脑子移植到我的身体里
什么? 脑部移植手术?
是的，这是最有争议的手术
这太可笑了
可笑的是你三个半月没有做过爱
现在是冬天，街上的人少了很多
他们要踢走谁?
西西雅梦露，她饰演洁西卡拉哈特
不!
她是我最喜欢的角色了
不错
她最擅长将饮料泼到别人脸上
我从来没看过她喝完一杯饮料
还有她打人巴掌的样子，你不想那么做吗?
不要乱来
西西雅梦露，多好的演员啊 没错
她参与这部戏的演出很久了
要代替她一定很难
你得帮帮我
当你做过脑部移植手术后…
你要变成她?
对，她被困在德瑞克的身体里
你为什么就是搞不懂? 我还以为你是科学家
Friends.S07E15 乔伊的新大脑
瑞秋，那边那个男的…
异性恋还是同性恋?
应该是同性恋
是吗? 为什么?
主要是因为他在亲别的男人
不，那里没有别的男人．那人就在那里
他太帅了，不可能是异性恋
大波霸小姐会帮我们查个清楚
好了，他是异性恋
而且一眼就看得出来
他忘了拿手机
我们得把它交给甘瑟，放在失物招领处
或是用它打电话到中国看看那些人在做什么?
如果他打电话来找手机，我接了电话…
我们开始聊天，之后坠入爱河呢?
那是个很棒的故事吧?
就像是神仙故事时代的童话故事
那听起来很棒，我要去拿手机
什么? 等一下 为什么你会成为故事的女主角
我已经很久没有约会了
菲比，三天前你才约过会
那不是约会，那只是朋友聚会，然后做爱
好吧，我去拿手机
不行，一星期前你才跟泰格分手
对，直到现在，我才明白，我能再爱一次
说的好等一下
我们该怎么公平地决定，谁能拿走手机呢?
我不知道
或许我们可以…
你动作太慢了!
你太自大了
我在跟他约会，你管不了
不，我管得了
你打算怎么做? 杀了他吗？ 就像你杀了查尔斯?
那是意外
你也好不到哪里去
至少我不是杀人犯
我的宝贝
卡!
你演得太好了，刚刚那一巴掌很逼真，你怎么办到的?
那只是多年的经验快拿冰块过来给我
我想说我觉得你的演技很棒
你该不会是那个快死掉的影迷吧?
我要会见并拥抱一个快死的影迷
但那不应该是以后的事
我是乔伊崔比亚尼，昨天我们合拍过一场戏
我就是那个昏迷的人那是真人?
因为你离开后我要移植你的脑子…
我在想如果…
我要离开? 为什么? 你听到了什么?
是谁告诉你的?
编剧之一 哪个编剧? 是秃头佬还是高个子?
那不重要，因为那不是真的
好吧
如果那是真的，你竟然敢来叫我教你…
该如何饰演我演了二十年的角色
梦露小姐…哦，你真的那么做了
不，菲比，你不能那样拿走电话 那不公平
好吧，听着，我有个点子
我们为什么不看看 他的速拨键记录了哪些电话号码，
跟他有最多共通点的人，就可以把手机拿走
或者看谁的名字最接近“电话”那个字（与“菲比”最接近）
我不那样认为
好吧．不过我肯定你还会闹的
速拨键的第一个名字是“妈妈”
哦，我妈妈自杀死了
不行，你不能利用那一点抢走帅哥跟最后一块蓝萄松饼
今天我已经用过那个借口了? 对不起
好了，你看，还没有结果
“乔，卡洛斯，瑜伽，班” 等一下，我练瑜伽．那是我的
好吧．哦，差一点，如果是“优格”就好了（酸奶酪）
“彼德．鲁格”，那是猪扒店
好吧，肉食者．这个是你的
我赢了，他在速拨键里记下了巴尼斯
你不知道他指的是不是巴尼斯服饰店
那可能是他朋友家或是酒吧的电话…
谁会把巴尼斯服饰店的电话记录成速拨键?
他的新女朋友
那是什么声音?
我想是快死掉的猫在举行游行
听起来是从对街传来的
我的天啊什么?
还记得罗斯说他要在婚礼上我给我们惊喜吗?
他跟我出去混时说：“你有苏格兰的血统吧?”
不是的!
不，不可能，不可能是罗斯
不可思议，为什么你有苏格兰血统?
为什么罗斯是你哥哥?
他不能在婚礼上演奏，大家都会跑光的
就好像指责我不守戒律（犹太教）
不能跟他说不．他可能会练习一辈子的，那样他就完了
也许有可以不伤害他感情的方法
别这样，那只是噪音!
那根本不算是歌
等一下，如果你仔细听…
我想它是“库尔与伙伴”合唱团唱的《庆祝》
吨，你好吗? 我很好
还记得我们在咖啡厅时…
我们决定我可以拿走那个帅哥的手机吗?
我要把它放在我的皮包里 如果它响了，我就能立刻接听
你还记得你从我的皮包把手机偷走了吗?
我听不懂你在说什么?
你偷走了手机不，我没有
如果我拨号过去它不会响吗?
不会 好吧
既然你要拨号了 我要让你看看我刚买的响铃皮包
噢，它真的有用
菲比 那是另一只手机
是吗? 喂，对，你好，瑞秋在吗?
她在，请稍等，是找我的
那是铁证
我的天哪，一定是他
我的神仙童话故事就要开始了
该怎么样说呢? 就说“你好”?
或者说，“嗨!我是瑞”?
你能不能别再那么做了?
喂，对，我就是捡到你手机的人
菲比，你不能…我在讲电话
对，今晚你能过来拿，就八点半吧?
到我家来
摩顿街五号，十四号房
或许之后我们可去吃点东西
好的，到时候见，再见
你知道他来的时候我会在这里
你怎么知道他什么时候会来?
你刚刚说出来了
好吧，我希望到时我能一个人呆
我要好好想想我母亲和她的自杀
噢，菲比! 什么? 那是今天第一次
你喜欢干酪辣玉米片?
我自己，则喜欢…我只有16岁
2003年见（此时是2001年，两年之后她就18岁成年了）
你说的对，他们要将我踢出这部戏
他们还没有决定什么时候，但应该很快…
就是这样了
我真的很抱歉，如果我可以决定 你永远都不会离开这部戏
谢谢你 我是认真的
我不敢相信他们会对你这么做还有你的影迷
他们一定会崩溃伤心，他们是那么地爱你
你说的对
谢谢
你说你叫什么名字?
乔伊谢谢你
那真的太贴心了
对不起
那不是我的决定 我在跟别人说话呢
你接着说
听着，之前我会来找你
是因为…
因为要饰演你我真的很紧张
请你帮我抓住角色的精髓
帮助我让洁西卡继续活下去，可以吗?
好吧，乔伊，我会帮你
不是因为我对这部蠢戏有亏欠…
而是因为我亏欠洁西卡
那真的是太棒了，谢谢你别客气
我一直在观摩录影带，你觉得这招如何?
洁西卡拉哈特永远都不会再踏入这里!
永远都不会!
那是我吗? 没错
但洁西卡没有英国腔
我有英国腔?
我要把这点写在我履历表里
我想吃点点心
你要吃点脆饼吗? 它是你故乡苏格兰的点心
不，谢谢，我不喜欢苏格兰的东西
什么?
因为我的家族被赶出苏格兰…
是维京人干的
总之，很多不好的回亿
听起来你家人准备要恢复办格兰传统
不，不，他们不会的
他们还非常愤怒
不过，你知道，钱德也有瑞典血统
知道瑞典人以什么著称吗?
安静的坐着
不过苏格兰历史非常…
你不能在婚礼上吹风笛!
你们怎么知道?
我们听到你在家里吹风笛是你们去报警的?
现在那真的不重要
重要的是，我们谢谢你的好意…
我们只是觉得我们的婚礼上不适合吹风笛
为什么? 因为我们讨厌风笛
别这样，那不公平．你们还没听过我的演奏
听过了
不，你们只是听过我练习而己
给我机会为你们表演，再做最后的决定
我也不会告诉你们，我要吹哪首曲子
就说当表演结束后…
我们一定会庆祝一下
这个角色的精髓派自于她的自信
譬如说，当洁西卡走进一个房间时…
她拥有那个房间里…
所有事物跟所有人
你来试试看好吧
不错
不．他已经知道他拥有房间里的一切
他不是第一次发现
再来试一次 好的
他没有对这个房间生气
再试一次，他拥有它，他拥有这个房间
这是他的，他拥有这个房间! 他拥有它!
这有点奇怪，但已经好多了
我一定会想念这个女人 我不知道我该怎么办
我演这部戏二十年了
或许这是件好事
它给你机会做改变扮演不一样的角色
你才华横溢
是的，没错
但是我不知道．你知道…
…上了年级的演员，不容易啊
那不是真的．看看安洁拉・兰斯布（著名英国演员） 安吉丽娜・朱莉（奥斯卡最佳女配角）
或许我该在几年前离开那时候很多人要我接戏．
但我在这里过得太舒服…
我拒绝了一些大好机会
譬如说呢?
哦，就说如果我在十五年前离开…
现在墨西哥影坛会完全不一样
哇
但现在…现在时机不一样了
嘿，别这样
听我说句话，好吗?
当我看到你演戏时，我想“天啊，她是个很棒的演员”
但我也会想“她好辣”
你觉得我很辣?
你拥有这个房间
或许我们应该…
对，我们应该…
当洁西卡吻男人时…
她通常会把…
双手放在那个男人脸上
我注意到了，那是因为她充满了热情吗?
不，那是因为那样子摄影机只能拍到她
你想试试看吗?
好的
太棒了，真的很不错
但我想你手的位置不对，它们应该…
嘿
是谁?
我是汤姆，我来拿手机的
为什么要由你去开门?
为什么不行? 因为这里是我家
那么由我来把手机交给他
好吧，希望你能好好跟他解释那些打到中国的电话
嗨
我们争执了多久?
你不是那个忘了拿手机的人
对，他是我的助理他会来吗?
不会
你能让我们谈一下吗? 没问题
我们马上回来
我们该怎么办? 我不知道
你能相信吗?
我们在等一个帅哥 结果来了一个超级大帅哥
我知道
什么?
他们不再喜欢那样了，知道吗?
不．他们喜欢．不过你要等待
瑞秋，听我说…
如果你能把他让给我我真的欠你一个大人情
好吧
好吧，我把他让给你
但你欠我一个大人情
好的，你真是好朋友
哪一位漂亮的小姐要陪我去吃晚餐?
是我
你先请谢谢
太棒了
你的确拥有那个房间
事实上我租下整问公寓我刚了解你的意思，谢谢夸奖
嗨 嘿
我的天啊
洁西卡拉哈特! 在我家里面!
我是你的头号大影迷，我是你的头号大影迷
很高兴能知道…
莫妮卡!
她是我的室友瑞秋
难怪你家会有女人内衣
没错
我的天啊，是真的!
我的天哪，你太迷人了
我的天啊，我能请你帮我一个忙吗?
当然可以
你能打我一巴掌吗?
我很乐意，但我的律师说 我不能再那么做了
天哪，看上去你真的非常好人
好了，再见
我是说，不像其他名人那样做作
好了，我们走
不，等一下，还有一件事
你是个笨女人我真的不能打你巴掌
你真漂亮 很高兴见到你
我的天啊，你太棒了谢谢你们过来
我真的很抱歉不
我习惯被影迷包围，别担心
我的天啊什么?
他们富了今天的剧本来给我他们从来没有富剧本给过我
是吗? 我一直都昏迷不醒
这代表我有台词了
我是怎么死的?
你摔下马，然后撞到电篱笆
什么? 洁西卡讨厌马
经过这件事，她也不会喜欢电
请记住，你们要想象我穿着苏格兰裙
我想象你穿着短格子花呢衬衫和到膝的袜子
你要开始讲秘密吗? 不
请记住…
我还在学吹风笛
一，二，三，四!
你们都知道这首歌，一起唱吧
怎么样?
不 不
在妈妈的马鞍上动手脚是个超级好点子，佛莱德克
电篱笆那个点子太妙了
谢谢你，亲爱的
我不敢相信她真的死了
看看你的四周，一切都是你的
我可不那么认为
你是谁?
怎么了?  笛娜
你不认得你自己的…
妈妈吗?
卡! 大家都演得很好，谢谢
那真的是太棒了
我想你比我更适合演洁西卡
喔，不当然不是，但你真的很棒
谢谢
好消息，我找到新工作了
太棒了，是什么样的工作
我要到瓜达拉哈拉（墨西哥西部城市）拍电影
你是指那个机场?
不，那是拉瓜迪亚机场
我要去墨西哥 哇
你会去多久?
八个月
那真的很久对，但你可以来看我
我敢说你能在那里拥有几个地方
你知道的，或许我该先在纽约买房子
我刚了解你的意思，那…
那真的有难度真的很难
乔伊，我真的要谢谢你
你减少了我在困境中的痛苦
祝你好运
你也是
Thanks for coming by.
We wanted to bounce some ideas off
of you about the wedding ceremony.
- What's the matter? Are you okay?
- It's just...
Monica said, "wedding."
We thought one of you
could read something.
I would love to read a poem.
Do you think you could
get through a poem?
A short one.
Okay, so Ross will be doing the reading.
Okay, yeah, I guess I can do that too.
Too?
I kind of have something else
planned for you guys.
- Do you mind telling us what it is?
- Sorry.
I'm kind of keeping this one
on the q. T.
Whatever it is,
I hope it involves winking.
- Hey.
I talked to one of the DOOL writers...
- What is DOOL?
- Days of Our Lives.
You're not gonna believe it. My character
is coming out of his coma!
- That's wonderful.
- Wow, Joey.
And not only that,
I'm getting a new brain!
So great things are happening at work
and in your personal life.
You're getting a new brain?
They're killing off
one of the characters on the show...
...and her brain is being transplanted
into my body.
What? A brain transplant?
Yes, it's a highly controversial procedure.
It's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous that you
haven't had sex in three and a half months.
It's winter.
There are fewer people on the street.
Who are they killing off?
Cecilia Monroe.
She plays Jessica Lockhart.
No!
She's my favorite character on DOOL.
Nice.
She is so good at throwing drinks
in people's faces.
I don't think I've ever seen
her finish a beverage.
The way she slaps people.
Wouldrt you love to do that?
Don't do it.
- Cecilia Monroe, what a great actress.
- Tell me about it.
And she's been on the show forever.
It's gonna be really hard
to fill her shoes.
Help me out here.
When you come out
of the brain transplant...
...you are going to be her?
Yes, but in Drake Ramoray's body.
Why is this so hard for you to get?
I thought you were a scientist.
S07E15 The One With Joey's New Brain
Rach, so that guy there...
...straight or gay?
Well, I'd have to say gay.
Yeah? Why?
Mainly because he's kissing
that other guy.
Oh, no, not that guy there.
That guy right there.
Oh, yeah, he's too cute
to be straight.
Knockers will help us
figure it out.
All right, straight.
And not subtle.
He left his cell phone.
We could hand it to Gunther
to put it in lost and found.
Or we could use it to call China,
see how those guys are doing.
What if he calls his own cell phone
and I answer...
...and we start talking
and we fell in love?
Wouldrt that be a great story?
Kind of like a fairy tale
for the digital age.
That does sound great.
I'm gonna get the phone.
What? Wait.
Why do you get the story?
I haven't been
out on a date in so long.
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
That wasrt a date. That was friends
getting together and having sex.
Okay. Great. I get the phone.
No way. You just broke up with Tag
a week ago.
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think
I would love again.
- Nice try.
- Wait.
How do we fairly decide
who gets the phone?
I don't know.
Maybe we could...
Aha! Too slow!
Aha! Too cocky.
I'm dating him.
There's nothing you can do.
Yes, there is.
What are you going to do, kill him?
Like you did Charles?
That was an accident.
And so were you.
Well, at least I'm not a murderer.
Oh, my baby.
Cut!
That was a great scene. That slap looked
so real. How do you do that?
- Oh, just years of experience.
- Can I get some ice here?!
I just wanted to say how wonderful
I think you are.
You're not the fan who's dying,
are you?
I'm supposed to meet
and hug a fan who's dying.
But that's not suppose to be until later.
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
We did a scene together yesterday.
- I'm the guy in the coma.
- Oh, that was a real person?
Since I'm getting your brain
when you leave the show...
...I was wondering if...
- I'm leaving the show?
- Why? Did you hear something?
Who told you that?
- One of the writers.
- Which writer? Was it bald or was it tall?
You know, it doesn't matter,
because it is not true.
Okay.
And if it were true, how dare you come
to me and ask me for tips...
...about a character I've played
for 20 years!
Miss Monroe...
Oh, there you go.
No, Phoebe, you cannot get the phone
that way. That's not fair.
Okay, look, I have an idea.
Why don't we see what kind of numbers
he has on his speed dial...
...and then whoever has more in common
with him gets the phone.
Or we can decide by whoever's name
is closer to the word "phone."
I don't think so.
Fine. But I bet you'd be singing a different
tune if we were fighting over a ratchet.
First name on the speed dial is "Mom."
Oh. I lost my mom to suicide.
No way. You can't use that to get the cute
guy and the last blueberry muffin.
Did I use that already today? I'm sorry.
Well, now, see,
this isn't telling us anything.
- "Joe. Carlos. Yoga. Ben..."
- Wait. I do yoga. That's one for me.
Oh, all right.
Oh, so close. If only it said, "yogurt."
"Peter Luger." That's a steak house.
Okay, fine. Meat-eater.
Fine, that's one for you.
Oh, I win. He's got Barneys
on his speed dial.
You don't know it's Barneys
the store.
That could be his friend's
house or a bar...
Who has Barneys the store
on their speed dial?
His new girlfriend.
What is that?
I think it's the Dying Cat Parade.
Sounds like it's coming
from across the street.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
The thing that Ross was gonna
do at our wedding?
He was hanging out with me and said,
"You're half Scottish, right?"
- No.
- Yes!
No. There is no way.
It cannot be Ross.
Unbelievable.
Why is your family Scottish?
Why is your family Ross?
He cannot play at our wedding.
Everyone will leave.
It'll be like when he rapped
at my bat mitzvah.
We can't just tell him no. He's probably
been practicing forever. He'll be crushed.
Maybe there's a way we can tell him
without hurting his feelings.
I mean, come on. That is just noise!
It's not even a song.
Wait. If you listen very carefully...
...I think it's "Celebration"
by Kool and the Gang.
- Hi. How are you?
- Good.
Remember when we were
in the coffeehouse...
...we decided I was gonna keep
the cute guy's phone?
I was gonna keep it in my purse so if
it rang, I could just pick it up?
Do you remember going into my purse
and stealing the phone?
Now you lost me.
- You stole the phone.
- No, I didn't.
You're saying that if I called it,
it wouldn't ring?
- No.
- Okay.
But while you dial, let me show you
the features of my new ringing handbag.
Oh, it does work.
- Phoebe.
- That is a different phone.
Oh, is it? Hello. Yes, hi,
is Rachel there?
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please.
It's for me!
That is damning evidence.
Oh, my God. I bet that's him.
My digital fairy tale's
about to begin.
I wonder how it should be?
Should I be, "Hello"?
Or should I be, "Hi! It's Ra..."?
Would you stop doing that?
Hello? Yes, I'm the one
who found your phone.
- Phoebe, you can't...
- I'm on a call.
Yeah, you can pick it up tonight.
Say, 8:30?
At my apartment.
It's 5 Morton Street,
apartment 14.
And then maybe, you know, after,
we can grab a bite to eat or whatever.
Okay. Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
You do know that I will be here
when he comes over.
How will you know what time
to come over?
You just said it.
Well, I was kind of hoping
that I would just be alone.
You know, to think about my mom
and her suicide.
- Oh, Phoebe!
- What? That's the first time today.
So you like the nachos, huh?
- Myself, I'm partial to...
- I'm 16.
See you in 2003.
You're right.
They are writing me out of the show.
They don't know exactly when
it's going to happen, but soon...
...and then that's it.
I'm so sorry. If it was up to me,
you would never leave the show.
- Yeah, thanks.
- I mean it.
I can't believe they'd do this to you.
And to your fans.
They're gonna be devastated.
Heartbroken. They love you so much.
Oh, you're right.
Thank you.
What's your name again?
- Joey.
- Thank you.
That is so sweet.
Excuse me.
- It wasrt my decision.
- I'm having a conversation here.
You were saying.
Look, the only reason
I came up to you before...
...is because, well...
...l'm really nervous about being you.
If you could help me capture
the essence of the character, you know.
Help me keep Jessica alive.
Please?
All right, Joey, I'll help you.
Not because I owe it
to this stupid show...
...but because I owe it to Jessica.
- Oh, that's great. Thank you so much.
- You're so welcome.
I've been watching some tapes.
How's this?
Jessica Lockhart will never
step foot in this place again!
Never!
- Is that supposed to be me?
- Yeah.
But Jessica doesn't have
an English accent.
I can do an English accent?
That baby's going on my resume.
Well, I feel like a snack.
Do you want some shortbread?
It's Scottish, like you are.
Oh, no, thanks. I don't like anything
from my Scottish heritage.
What?
Well, it's just that my entire family
was run out of Scotland by...
...Vikings.
Anyway, lots of bad memories.
It sounds to me like your family's ready
to rediscover its Scottish roots.
No. No, they're not.
They're still very angry.
But, you know, Chandler's also
half-Swedish.
You know what the Swedish people
are famous for?
Sitting down and being quiet.
Yeah, but the Scottish history
is so much...
You can't play bagpipes
at the wedding!
How did you know about that?
- We heard you play from your apartment.
- Were you the ones who called the cops?
That's not really important right now.
What is important is, while we
appreciate the gesture...
...we just don't feel that bagpipes
are appropriate for our wedding.
- Why not?
- Because we hate them.
Come on, that's not fair.
You haven't even heard me play.
We have heard you play.
No, you've heard me practice.
Just give me a chance to perform for
you, then decide whatever you want.
I'm not gonna tell you what song
I'm gonna play either.
Let's just say when it's over...
...l'll bet there'll be
a wee bit of celebration.
The essence of the character
is rooted in her confidence.
So when Jessica enters a room,
for instance...
...she owns everything...
...and every person in that room.
- You try it.
- Okay.
All right!
No. He already knows
that he owns everything in the room.
He's not finding it out for the first time.
- So try it again.
- Okay.
He's not angry at the room either.
Try it again. He owns it.
He owns the room.
It is his. He owns, owns,
owns the room! He owns it!
It's a little weird,
but it's getting better.
I'm gonna miss this woman so much.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
It's been 20 years of my life.
Hey, hey. Maybe this is a good thing.
It'll give you a chance to shake
things up. Play different characters.
You're so talented.
I am, I am.
But I don't know. You know...
...an actor of a certain age,
it's not that easy.
That's not true. Look at Angela Lansbur...
Angelina Jolie.
Probably should've just left years ago
when the offers were pouring in...
...but I just got
so comfy here and...
I turned down some amazing work.
Like what?
Well, let's just say
if I'd left 15 years ago...
...the landscape of Mexican
cinema would be very different today.
Wow.
But, well, now...
Now's a different time for me.
Oh, hey, come on. Don't do this.
Let me tell you something, okay?
When I watch you do a scene,
I'm thinking, "Boy, she is a great actress."
But I'm also thinking, "She is hot."
You think I'm hot?
You own the room.
We should probably get the...
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we should get...
So when Jessica kisses a man...
...she usually puts...
...both her hands on the mars face.
I notice that.
Is that because she's so passionate?
No, it's because that way
the camera only sees her.
You want to try it?
Yeah, okay.
That was good. That was really good.
But I think that maybe your hands
are just a little off. They should be right...
Hey, hey!
Who is it?
It's Tom.
I'm here to pick up the phone.
Why do you get to answer the door?
- Why shouldn't I?
- Because it's my apartment.
Then I get to give him the cell phone.
Okay. Good luck explaining
all the calls to China.
Hi.
Wow, how long were we arguing for?
You're not the man who left the phone.
- No, that's my assistant.
- Is he coming?
No.
- Could you give us one second?
- Sure.
We'll be right back, sir.
- What do we do?
- I don't know.
Can you believe this?
We were waiting for a hot guy,
and then an even hotter one shows up.
I know.
What?
They just don't make them
like that anymore, you know?
No, they do,
but you just have to wait.
Rachel, listen...
...if you let me have him,
then I will really owe you one.
All right.
All right, I will let you have him.
But you owe me. You owe me big.
Yeah. You're such a great friend.
Which one of you lovely ladies am I taking
to dinner?
Oh, that'd be me, sir.
- After you.
- Oh, thank you.
Nice.
Well, you certainly own that room.
Actually, I rent the whole place.
I just got what you meant. Thank you.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Jessica Lockhart!
In my apartment!
I am such a huge fan.
It's nice to know...
Monica!
That's my roommate, Rachel.
That explains all the womers underwear.
Sure.
Oh, my God, it's true!
Oh, my God, you are so amazing.
Can I just ask you to do me
just one favor?
Certainly.
Would you slap me
right here in the face?
I'd love to, but my lawyer said
I can't do that anymore.
God, you seem really, really nice.
Okay, bye-bye.
I mean, not fake at all
like most famous people.
All right, here we go.
No, wait. Just one more thing.
- You're a stupid bitch.
- I really can't slap you.
- You are so beautiful.
- So nice to meet you.
- My God, you're great.
- Thanks for stopping by.
- I am so sorry about that.
- Oh, no.
Being adored, I'm used to it.
Don't worry about it.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
They sent me today's script.
They never send me the script.
- They don't?
- I'm just in a coma.
This must mean I have lines.
How does it happen?
You get thrown from a horse
into an electric fence.
A what? Jessica hates horses.
After this, she's not gonna be crazy
about electricity either.
Now, remember,
you have to imagine me in a kilt.
I can imagine you in a short plaid skirt
and knee socks.
- You wanna start telling secrets?
- No.
Now, remember...
...l'm still learning.
One, two, three, four!
You know the song. Sing along.
So?
- No.
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse
was brilliant, Fredrick.
And the electric fence, inspired.
Thank you, sweetheart.
I can't believe she's really gone.
Look around you. All of this is ours.
I don't think so.
Who are you?
What's the matter, Dina?
Don't you recognize your own...
...mother?
Cut! That was great, everybody.
Thank you.
That was so wonderful!
I think that you're a better
Jessica than I ever was.
- Oh, no.
- Of course not, but you were good.
Thanks.
Good news. I got another job.
Great. Hey, all right! What is it?
A film in Guadalajara.
The airport?
No, that's LaGuardia.
- This is Mexico.
- Oh, wow.
Well, how long will you be gone?
Eight months.
- That's a really long time.
- Yeah, but you could come and visit.
I bet that you could own
a few places down there.
Oh, you know, I should probably
buy a place in the city first.
And I just got what you meant.
That is...
- That's a tricky one.
- It's tricky.
Joey, I really want to thank you.
You made a very difficult time for me
a little less painful.
Good luck.
You too.